He looks so pissed off right now.
Yeah, like ready to punch pit.
I hate it when he comes here.
He so freaks me out.
Here we go again.
Same old, same old.
Same old attitudes about me.
Same old after school whatever.
Same old neighbor's club.
Hey, guys.
Sorry about that.
Wrong room.
Hey, get back here, Kodika.
Don't you like my hair?
Totally, yeah.
It looks great on you.
Well, thanks.
I mean, no.
I'm asking you if you think it's funny.
If it's funny?
Oppie, don't you remember yesterday
we were talking about making friends
by being funny and entertaining?
I remember.
So you did this?
Mm-hmm.
The sign at the toy store said
this was guaranteed to be a hit,
so I bought it.
You take this stuff too seriously.
I couldn't agree more.
As I suspected,
the distinguished art form known as comedy
is well beyond meat's capacity.
Oh, come on.
Not you two.
Today, I'm dressed as one of the most
laughable creatures ever to exist.
Tell the truth.
You know I'm hilarious right now.
Okay, then how about this?
You hooker.
I'm gonna murder you.
Whoa, it's me.
I'm just so, like, rich and pretty
and, like, oh, no.
You're so stupid.
I don't sound like that.
You're right.
I, like, so don't sound like that.
I sound more like this.
Oh, look at me.
I need attention.
I am not a laughable creature,
you big jerk.
Besides, you're not even funny.
You're just annoying like normal.
That's awesome.
Welcome to my world.
Now you can see how much fun
you're crying and bitching is
for the rest of us.
Shut up.
You're awful.
Hey, Yozara.
I'm surprised you're not embarrassed
to look that way.
Anyway, you know, girls,
true comedy is more than
just cheap gimmicks.
No one who looks like you
gets to be condescending.
Yeah, since you know so much,
why don't you show us
this mystical true comedy?
Oh, I can do that.
True comedy, now listen up,
is about talking.
Talking?
That's what I said.
Now get ready to laugh
your faces off.
So here we go.
Two nuns walk into a bar.
And then the priest said,
bless you, my child.
And the bartender said,
yeah, that's what she said.
Get it?
So lame.
Comedy, huh?
Rico agrees popular people do have a tendency to be rather funny.
Big Brother, here is your tea.
Thanks.
I wish I had been around to hear you tell your funny story.
Was it great?
No, count your blessings.
Truth, it was way beyond bad.
Hey, well, at least I did more than just change my stupid hairstyle like you guys did.
Hush, no one asked you.
Oh, speaking of hairstyles, I recently heard something pretty fascinating.
What did you hear?
I read a magazine that said this style called a poof is really popular right now.
You know, for people with actual lives.
A poof?
Well, you literally poof up your hair to make it all big.
And after you've got that crazy volume, you're supposed to put random decorations and stuff in it.
Weird, but it does sound kind of fun.
Rika's seen pictures of that all over the internet.
They almost remind Rika of medieval European nobility.
Seriously? Sounds like it's perfect for me.
There are historically super extreme versions of the poof, too.
Like they twist their hair up into an elaborate cage and then put a real-life bird in there and get it to flap around.
For real?
Why would they do that?
Rika supposes they wanted to emphasize individuality over functionality, a concept not unlike that of the Warring States helmets.
So basically this poof style, like the helmets of the Warring State Generals, was designed to serve as proof of identity for those brave souls who were tragically beheaded in battle.
That way their heads would receive the respect deemed appropriate for their position, not to mention their families...
That is in no way accurate.
That's a real shame.
Okay.
I mean, I don't totally get it, but I'll assume you guys do.
If you ask me, only like a really exceptional person would have the ability to pull off this look.
A boring old commoner would look ridiculous if they even tried, am I right?
Sorry if I'm annoying you with all this talk of something irrelevant to your life.
Anyways, the safest bet for an ordinary commoner would be to get an ordinary hairdo at an ordinary salon.
Still though, one day I hope I get the chance to see a poof in real life.
Rika does too, but it would be difficult.
There just aren't many people out there with the naturally aristocratic and gorgeous aura needed to carry such a look.
That class of intense self-assuredness is so hard to come by.
Preach, sister. What a crying shame.
They couldn't be more obvious.
I could pull off a poof.
It worked.
I'm an aristocrat who's like overflowing with awesome aura.
No one is better suited for the poof than me.
Don't strain yourself, me.
She's right, Senna.
The poof is an exceedingly tricky hairstyle and we don't want you to accidentally hurt yourself.
I'm not gonna get hurt!
The aura of divinity I project from within is enough to carry off anything,
much less some silly little fad hairstyle.
And this is why she's such an easy target.
Okay, well, if you're up for it, I don't mind poofing your hair for you right this minute.
Good idea!
Rika has all sorts of tools in her lab and we'll go get them!
Tools?
What for?
Okay, we're both ready if you are.
I'm ready.
Just don't go too crazy, okay?
Quit squirming meat.
This is gonna be fun.
Well, I have to admit it is pretty nice to have another girl brush your hair for you.
Oh, wow.
Rika can't believe how shiny and smooth your hair is, Senna.
Rika can't see a single split end.
Guess I can give you credit for good hair too, if nothing else.
Thanks.
Yelzara, your hair is also very pretty.
Rika's way jealous.
I guess it's not horrible, which makes it her one redeeming characteristic.
But don't sell yourself short, Rika, because your hair is awesome.
I told you not to move.
Is it really?
Here, a refill.
Thank you.
Thanks, that's really sweet.
All right, it's poofing time.
Any requests, meat?
I don't know.
You could try to make me look like someone who has a real life.
It has a life theme, huh?
Real lives make me think of... summer?
Yeah, that's perfect!
We can give it a whole girl who has a real life enjoying summer feel!
First, let's wave the sides to evoke the image of rolling ocean waves!
Yes, I like it.
Next, why don't we try putting in sassy little ringlets?
That'll represent the swirling times.
And this part can be a summer storm, so kind of flashy frizz!
What do you think of it, Senna?
I, uh... yeah, that works.
Not for the top.
Since the sides are the ocean, the top should be a sand castle on the beach.
How about we use a real bikini instead of plain old ribbons?
Oh yeah, and a watermelon and some fireworks to complete the picture.
A bikini and... and watermelon?
And why not some yakisoba while we're at it, right?
Totes right, you're a genius!
Well, I think...
Will you stop moving?
I'll go right now and purchase a bikini, a watermelon, and some yakisoba.
Thanks, bro.
Okay, what do you think about this here?
Yodika, help me!
Sorry, there's nothing I can do.
Poke, poke, poke, poke!
Fly! Go on, fly!
Excuse me.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I promise!
Look, I'm doing it just like I'm supposed to!
Oh, hey, Yukimura.
Hello, Sister Maria.
What are you doing out here?
What does it look like?
The old hags are forcing me into hard labor as punishment for slacking off.
So that's my story.
What are you doing?
Well, all the girls in the club, blah, blah, blah, and so forth.
Oh, I have a bunch of summery things!
Look at these!
You can totally take them with you!
Go, go, go, go, go!
All done!
Okay, it's called the ultimate satisfying social life meets midsummer night's dream mega poop.
Mega-Poof.
OMG, Senna, you look super adorbs.
Wow, that is not right.
I can't get over the gorgeous.
Your head would make a most magnificent war trophy.
Thanks, guys.
It really looks that good?
Really? It's beautiful.
Wow, your hair's not simply gaudy.
It's also poignant and inspirational.
I gotta say I agree.
And I'm jealous.
I wish I'd try to poof before I cut all my hair off.
Yeah, I think it's a winner. I love it.
They've all lost their minds.
What do you think of my poof, Kodika?
Uh, um, it expresses the group aesthetic.
I mean, like, right?
Okay, bye, guys. I'm going home now.
I hope she'll be all right.
Ah, Kodika!
Oh, hey, what's wrong?
Get this.
Daddy was so mad at me when I got home yesterday, like raging mad.
He spanked me hard and he made me put my hair back to normal.
It was the worst thing ever.
Wow, that blows.
All right, Pegasus. Good job.
Yesterday, Rika might have gotten a little too carried away.
But now that she's calmed down, she realizes it was wrong.
Yeah, I did the same thing.
We're very sorry, Meat.
Why couldn't you guys at least let this be a funny ending?
Stupid!
And so the club meeting ended in disappointment.
You get me.
I guess I should go.
I see how it is.
Hey, what's up?
No, no, no, no, no!
Come back!
Where are you going?
No, get away from me!
Help!
What the hell is going on over here?
Did you hear that scream over the phone?
Did you think someone was kidnapped?
No, everyone's fine.
Yeah!
You get me.
I heard Sina's got the best GPA in our grade.
Cobito, I'm going to study out at Sina's place for a while this afternoon, okay?
Okay.
I don't suppose you'd want to come along with me.
What's wrong?
K-K-Ki.
My dearest other half and brother.
I bid you take care.
So in other words, you don't want to go.
No, I don't.
She scares me.
True enough.
Wow, Sina.
She really hates you.
Good afternoon.
Welcome back.
Hey, Kodaka, you're here.
Indeed he is, which makes it time to study.
Really?
You mean you're done with him already?
I am.
So what was that about?
Oh.
Daddy's always asking about you, so I figured he'd want some time with you.
Like maybe he'd want to talk to you himself this time.
What?
Sina, I am not always asking about Kodaka.
Yes.
Well, Hayato called and asked me to look after you.
So naturally, I'm concerned for your welfare.
I don't know if I'll ever get that guy.
All right, Kodaka.
Let's go get our study on in my room.
Here it is.
It's okay to come in.
Right.
Cool.
Walk through the door.
Wait.
Whoa.
That's messed up.
They're great pictures, right?
That jerk leg never lets her guard down, so it took me forever to get them.
Um, this seems healthy to you?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't it be silly?
Great.
She's a stalker.
This chick is seriously disturbed.
Now, what did you do this for again?
Wait, I forgot to show you this.
Right.
Is that the same one Yozara had?
I might have kind of bought it from her.
Perseverance for vengeance, right?
Oh, you mean like from that old story about the guy who kept feeding his anger against his father's killer until he finally got revenge?
He slept on firewood and ate weird stuff, didn't he?
Yep.
There you have it.
By staring at Yozara's stupid face every night when I go to sleep while inhaling the scent of the wig she wore.
I remember the humiliation she's put me through and psyched myself up about making her pay for her crimes one day.
I swear I'll make that jerk beg me for mercy.
Senna Kashiwazaki.
The reason we need the hot versus crazy scale.
Hey.
What?
Uh, oh, right, about this problem.
I already solved that one for you.
I know that, but I still kind of need to know how to solve it myself if I want to pass the final.
What?
How can you not understand something so easy?
Are you stupid or what?
Fine, never mind, I'll just do it myself.
Good, but try to do it faster.
Or a smart girl.
She is one awful teacher.
Excuse me.
I've brought refreshments for the two of you.
It's been a while, Kodika.
I trust all matters are progressing well.
Um, well, yeah, I guess so.
I understand.
Please use this if the need arises.
I hope you both enjoy yourselves.
Kodika, what did Stella just hand to you?
Huh?
N-nothing, it's nothing.
That woman has a way of freaking me out.
Come on, show it to me.
Stop!
No!
Let go of it!
Show it to me!
Uh...
What are you looking at, perv?
I...
I'm not looking at anything, Beardo.
Fine.
I'm sick of studying.
How about we play a game instead?
That's not why I came over here.
Well, I guess it's no biggie, as long as it's just a little break.
Found it!
Do you want to play this one?
Sure.
But be warned, I play that with my sister a lot.
I didn't know you were into this.
Well, I haven't had it very long.
Kobito's like a super huge fan of the anime, isn't she?
Oh, oh yeah.
I went ahead and got all the Blu-rays when I picked up the game,
but I haven't watched them yet.
I was waiting for the next time Kobito comes over.
Thank all things holy I didn't bring her with me.
Shatter the very soul of my enemy!
Nye, my breaker!
K.O.
You win!
Amateur!
Ten in a row for me, suck it sucker!
Yeah, pretty awesome considering you were a total noob in the beginning.
I can't help it that I'm a genius at everything I do.
I wish I could deny it, but I can't.
Crap, when did it get so late?
And we didn't get any studying done for finals at all.
Whatever, I've got to go home.
Excuse me.
Forgive me for another interruption, but dinner is ready to be served now.
You heard the lady.
You might as well eat before you head home.
Yeah, great.
Thank you for the meal, sir.
I should probably get back now.
Nonsense.
What?
You will be staying with us for the night.
I...
What?
You are staying here for the night.
Oh.
Right.
Why do I always get so thrown off when I'm in this house?
Uh, president?
I'm here to wash your back.
No, thanks a lot, but I'm actually good.
Yes, of course, you're circumspect as usual.
Hayato would be tossing this over at me without missing a beat.
Don't worry, we're all friends here.
Yeah, how good of friends.
How's that feel?
Uh, it's fine.
That's just fine, sir.
You know, it's rather funny.
This brings back memories of the very first time your father took me to a bathhouse with him.
By the way, Kodika?
Um, yeah?
Well, I'm curious.
Do you know whether or not my daughter is perhaps being bullied at school?
Huh?
No, I'm pretty sure nothing like that's happening.
I see.
The reason I'm asking is, well, the other day, Senna came home with fried squid and yakisoba piled on her head.
It may be difficult to believe, but it's true.
Wow.
I had no idea, sir.
She said, this is a super high-class hairstyle worthy of my greatness.
Angry, I scolded her, but now that I've calmed down, I've realized something.
The truth of the matter is that there's no way such a ridiculous hairstyle could exist.
My daughter is a very proud young woman.
I was worried she might have said those absurd things to hide the fact that she's, she's being bullied.
Yep, that makes sense.
Um, Mr. President?
Hmm?
Have you been inside Senna's room recently?
No, not since she's entered high school.
She doesn't really like me to go in there for some reason.
I imagine that's perfectly natural for a girl her age.
I hate to tell you this, sir, but your daughter's actually turned into a psychopathic stalker.
I probably shouldn't say that.
Uh, for what it's worth, sir, I don't think she's being bullied.
Probably.
I hope you're right.
I swear to you, if I ever saw Senna get bullied, I would step in and protect her.
So try not to worry, sir.
You would?
Of course you would!
She's in your care, Kodaka.
I know she'll be in good hands with you.
Yep, yeah.
In my care?
That seems like a lot of pressure.
Oh, whatever.
At this point, I had yet to realize that I was getting increasingly involved in a situation
that was way out of my control.
One day, Yozara, just you wait.
Don't forget to subscribe to my channel on my channel.
Perhaps you'll support more about her while I'm dealing with her.
Also, let me know my channel's SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO SEO.
Cosmic Creampage link is in the description.
Well, that's maybe a video on the participar channel.
Going away from me today, I don't think so far here.
I did not think so far.
With my envir电 anges, I need a video support.
This anime's second season is finally kicking off.
In season two, now that I've cut my hair and quit screwing around,
I'll be able to do cool stuff more worthy of the main heroine.
I'll be trusted in my rightful place as leader of the Neighbors Club
and maybe get a real life, too.
I might even get closer with Kodaka and have the best year of my whole life.
This is gonna be so rad.
Next time, Homo Game Club.
Man, I love this season.
...